translate.com 2011-05-29

# Privacy Statement | ENLASO

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for ENLASO Corporation and http://www.translate.com. We do not send unsolicited email (Spam). 

### Information Collection and Use

ENLASO Corporation is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement without your express permission or unless ordered by a court of law. 

[Top of page]

### Sharing

We do not share personally identifiable information about our clients or the performance of their email marketing campaigns with 3rd parties. We do not share or rent our clients' email address lists, which remain the clients' exclusive and confidential property.

[Top of page]

### Unsubscribe/Opt-out

All recipients of email transmitted are given the opportunity to unsubscribe (opt-out) at any time by clicking on a link at the bottom of the email. Recipients may also click on a link at the bottom of the email to view ENLASO Corporation's Privacy Policy.

[Top of page]

### Cookies

ENLASO Corporation uses cookies for the sole purpose of tailoring web content to match the user's browser capability. The cookies do not store personal information. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally-identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.

[Top of page]

### HTML and Link Detectors

ENLASO embeds HTML and link detectors in all email transmissions to help gauge the effectiveness of our email campaigns. The detectors track recipients' capability of receiving HTML messages and the number of HTML messages opened. The detectors also track the links that recipients click on within the email. The detectors do not collect any other information.

[Top of page]

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

[Top of page]

### Online Security

Online security is enhanced by our use of firewalls protecting all of the ENLASO Corporation servers. The physical servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure facility that only authorized network administrators have access to. This facility provides security 24 hours a day, 365 days a year and protects our servers against power outages by using automated backup power systems.

[Top of page]

### Offline Security

Client information and data is stored in a secure facility within the ENLASO Corporation offices. Only ENLASO Corporation employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are trained on our security and privacy practices.

[Top of page]

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or about ENLASO Corporation, please contact us directly at: phone (866-415-6820 x127) or email ([Marketing@translate.com](mailto:Marketing@translate.com)) .

[Top of page]
